So let's discuss a couple things real quick. This is Mayor Eric Adams of New York City. I don't like
his face. I don't like his politics. He does not want to acknowledge Jordan Neely's murder as a
murder even though the medical examiner has ruled it as a homicide. He's also an ex-cop.
Kathy Hochul is the governor of New York City and she said people who are homeless in our subways
many of them in the throes of a mental health episode and that's what I believe were some of
the factors involved here. There's consequences for behavior. This... Now listen I'm fully aware
that the people who believe that to be okay are not going to have their minds changed by me making
this video right? The murder of houseless person Justin Neely on the New York City subway was not
a consequence of his mental health episode. It was a consequence of his race and of his status.
And he should not have been killed for either of those reasons. Neither of them.
The minds that I'm hoping to change are those who believe that they don't need to vote or bother with
civic matters because the people who are saying these things and supporting this murder are people who
were voted into position. Terrible people they're not smarter than you. They're just more organized.